Guide to the Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013.
Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013
- Series I. Articles Submitted for Publication in RRPE
  - Subseries B: Numbered Articles Submitted And Accepted, (originally submitted to specific RRPE issues)
    - ASSA - Demir, Firat. "The Rise of Rentier Capitalism and the Financialization of Real Sectors in Developing Countries", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 104)
    - ASSA - Saros, Daniel. "The Price-Form as a Fractional Reflection of the Aggregate Value of Commodities", 2007 (Box 33, Folder 105)
    - ASSA - Case, Karl. "Response to Guerrien and Benicourt", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 106)
    - ASSA - Katzner, Donald. "On the Analytical and Methodological Significance of Microeconomic Theory", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 107)
    - ASSA - Benicourt, Emmanuelle and Guerrien, Bernard. "Guerrien and Benicourt, Katzner, and Case: A Joint Response", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 108)
    - ASSA - Moseley, Fred. "Debate Over Microeconomics", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 109)
    - ASSA - Quick, Paddy. "Unpaid, Reproductive, Caring Labor? The Production of Labor Power?", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 110)
    - ASSA - Goldstein, Jonathan. "Heterodox Macroeconomics: Crotty's Integration of Keynes and Marx", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 111)
    - ASSA - Nakarani, Paulo and Herrera, Remy. "Structural Changes and Planning in Revolutionary Venezuela", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 112)
    - ASSA - Koont, Sinan. "A Cuban Success story: Urban Agriculture:, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 113)
    - ASSA - Campbell, Al. "The Cuban Economy: Where It Stands Today", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 114)
    - ASSA - Demir, Firat. "South-South Intra-Industry Trade in Manufactures", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 115)
    - ASSA - Mutari, Ellen and Figart, Deborah. "Transformations in Casino Gaming and the Unionization of Atlantic City's Dealers" ", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 116)
    - ASSA - Russell, Ellen. "Finance As Servant? Lessons From New Deal Financial Reform", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 117)
    - ASSA - Hillard, Michael and McIntyre, Richard. "The Limited Capital-Accord: May It Rest In Peace?", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 118)
    - ASSA - Vernengo, Matias. "Puzzles, Paradoxes and Regularities: Cyclical and Structural Productivity in the US", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 119)
    - ASSA - Koechlin, Timothy and Larudee, Mchrene. "Low Wage Labor and the Geography of Production", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 120)
    - ASSA - Kaboub, Fadhel. "Elements of a Radical Counter-Movement to Neoliberalism", 2008 (Box 33, Folder 121)
    - ASSA - Barkin, David. "Principles for Constructing Alternative Socio-Economic Organizations", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 122)
    - ASSA - King, Mary. "Betwixt and Between: The Spectrum of Formality Revealed in the Labor Market", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 123)
    - ASSA - Goldstein, Don. "Weirton Revisited: Finance, the Working Class, and Rustbelt Steel Restructuring", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 124)
    - ASSA - Larudee, Mehrene. "Sources of Polarization of Income and Wealth: Offshore Financial Centers"", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 125)
    - ASSA - Campbell, Al. "The Bush Business Cycle Profit Rate", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 126)
    - ASSA - O'Hara, Phillip. "The Global Securitized Subprime Market Crisis", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 127)
    - ASSA - Vasudevan, Ramaa. "Dollar Hegemony, Financialization and the Credit Crisis", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 128)
    - ASSA - Miller, John. "Leaving the Sphere of Exchange with David Houston, Karl Marx, and Even Adam Smith", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 129)
    - ASSA - Kotz, David. "The Financial and Economic Crisis of 2008", 2009 (Box 33, Folder 130)
    - ASSA - Grieve, Roy. "Time to Ditch ADAS?", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 131)
    - ASSA - Scarth, William. "Aggregate Demand-Supply Analysis and Its Critics: An Evaluation of the Controversy", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 132)
    - ASSA - Ramey, Elizabeth. "Seeds of Change: Hybrid Corn, Monopoly, and the Hunt for Superprofits", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 133)
    - ASSA - Gezici, Armagan. "Distributional Consequences of Financial Crises: Evidence from Recent Crises", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 134)
    - ASSA - Paulani, Leda Maria. "Brazil in the Crisis of the Finance-Led Regime of Accumulation", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 135)
    - ASSA - Baiman, Ron. "Toward a New Political Economy for the U.S.", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 136)
    - ASSA - Olsen, Erik. "Class Conflict and Industrial Location", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 137)
    - ASSA - Hopkins, Barbara. "The Institutional Barriers to Heterodox Pluralism", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 138)
    - ASSA - Kepeller, Jakob. "Some Critical Notes on Citation Metrics and Heterodox Economics", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 139)
    - ASSA - Moseley, Fred. Criticisms of Aggregate Demand and Aggregate Supply and Mankiw's Presentation", 2010 (Box 33, Folder 140)
    - #2226 - Penner, Devin. "The Limits of Radical Institutionalism", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - #2300 - Paterson, Stephanie. "Rethinking the Dynamics of Abusive Relationships", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - #2312b - Reviewed by Strachan, Ian. "Globalization and the Welfare State", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - #2420 - Teixeira, Rodrigo Alves; Rotta, Tomas. "Valueless Knowledge-Commodities and Financialization, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - #2435 - Akkermans, Dirk. "Subcontracting and the Creation of Inequality in the Dutch Clothing Industry", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - #2455 - Dang, Aimin. "Social Dividend Based on Overproduction", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - #2461 - Dunn, Bill. "Value Theory in an Incomplete Capitalist System", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - #2469 - McKenzie, Rex. "Casino Capitalism with Derivatives: Fragility and Instability in Contemporary Finance", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - #2471 - Chakraborthy, Saumya. "A Macroeconomic Framework of Employment", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - #2474 - Piovani, Chiara. "One Hundred Million Jobs for the Chinese Workers", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - #2478 - Hart-Landsberg, Martin. "Chinese Reform Experience: A Critical Assessment", 2008 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - #2481 - Hisnanick, John. "Who Are the Winners and the Losers? Transitions in the U.S. Household Income Distribution", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - #2486 - Das, Raju. "Reconceptualizing Capitalism: Forms of Subsumption of Labor, Class Struggle and Uneven Development", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - #2500 - Lo, Dic. "Making Sense of China's Economic Transformation", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - #2506 - Moseley, Fred. "The Determination of the Monetary Expression of Labor Time", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - #2507 - Kotz, David; Zhu, Andong. "The Dependence of China's Economic Growth on Exports and Investment", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - #2533b - Reviewed by Schneider, Aaron. "Ideas, Policies, and Economic Development in the Americas", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - #2536b - Reviewed by Bradbury, Mathew. "Monetary Integration and Dollarization: No Panacea", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - #2540 - Neilson, David. "Remaking the Connections: Marxism and the French Regulation School", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - #2545 - Branco, Manuel. "Economics Against Democracy", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - #2549 - Marquetti, Adalmir. "Participatory Economic Democracy in Action", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - #2553 - Miller, Glenna. "Gender Trouble: Investigating Gender and Economic Democracy in Worker Cooperatives in the U.S.", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - #2556b - Reviewed by Ganley, Bill. "The Origins of Capitalism and the Rise of the West", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - #2557 - Nesvetailova, Anastasia. "Minsky in the Shadows: Securitization, Ponzi Finance and the Crisis of Northern Rock", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - #2560b - Reviewed by Reati, Angelo. "Monetary Economics: An Integrated Approach to Credit, Money, Income, Production and Wealth", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - #2562b - Reviewed by Lajeunesse, Robert. "The Political Economy of Work", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - #2563 - Rohit. "Income Distribution, Irrational Exuberance and Growth", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - #2564 - Stockhammer, Engelbert. "Goodwin or Kalecki in Demand? Functional Income Distribution and Aggregate Demand in the Short Run", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - #2566b - Reviewed by Hart-Landsberg, Martin. "Adam Smith in Beijing", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - #2565b - Reviewed by Mohun, Simon. "Global Political Economy: A Marxist Critique", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - #2569b - Reviewed by Erten, Bilge. "Adam Smith in Beijing", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - #2570 - Lee, Frederic. "Heterodox Economics, Tolerance and Pluralism: A Reply to Garnett and Mearman", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - #2570b - Reviewed by Mearman, Andrew. "Pluralism, Plurality, Heterodoxy and the Rhetoric of Distinction", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - #2570 - Garnett, Robert. "Pluralism, Academic Freedom, and Heterodox Economics", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - #2572b - Reviewed by Fischler, Rafhael. "Riane Eisler, The Real Wealth of Nations: Creating a Caring Economics", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - #2576b - Reviewed by Sherman, Steven. "American Empire and the Political Economy of Global Finance", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - #2580b - Reviewed by Spangler, Eve. "Never Good Enough: Health Care Workers and the Promise of Job Training", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - #2581b - Reviewed by Chilvers, Simon. "Althusser: The Detour of Theory", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - #2583 - Pisani, Michael. "Revisiting the Mexican Informality Continuum in the United States", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - #2584b - Reviewed by Koechlin, Tim. "Superior Alternatives", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - #2585b - Reviewed by Milan, Marcelo. "How Much Money Does an Economy Need?", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - #2588b - Reviewed by Martin, Philip. "Coping with Facts: A Skeptic's Guide to the Problem of Development", 2009 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - #2593 - Hahnel. Robin. "Left Clouds Over Climate Change Policy", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - #2595b - Reviewed by Kramer, Brent. "Economic Literacy: Basic Economics With an Attitude", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - #2596 - Donnaruma, Colin. "Challenging the Presumption in Favor of Markets", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - #2600b - Reviewed by Moseley, Fred. "Marx's Grundrisse", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - #2602 - Morin, Philippe. "The Fonds de Solidarite: Historical and Political Foundations", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - #2603 - Dequattro, Art. "Market Socialism is not Market Capitalism", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - #2608 - Tsoulfidis, Lefteris. "The Growth of Unproductive Activities", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - #2609b - Reviewed by Fabien, Tarrit. "A Philosophical Defense of Market Socialism", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - #2610b - Reviewed by Waterman, Peter. "Globalization and Labor: Great Transformations?", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - #2611b - Reviewed by Chester, Lynne. "The Hardship of Nations: Exploring the Paths of Modern Capitalism", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - #2612b - Reviewed by Chester, Lynne. "Sustainable Capitalism: A Matter of Common Sense", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - #2616b - Reviewed by Black, Simon. "Global Unions", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - #2618b - Reviewed by Ghosh, Jayati. "Employment Targeted Economic Program for Kenya", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - #2620b - Reviewed by Larudee, Mehrene. "Capital as Power", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - #2621b - Revieweed by Mavroudeas, Stavros. "Economic Growth and Distribution", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - #2623b - Reviewed by Cochrane, D. T. "Shock of the Old: Technology and Global History Since 1900", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - #2624 - Lucarelli, Bill. "Financialization and Global Imbalances", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - #2625 - Wilson, Tamar Diana. "Primitive Accumulation and the Labor Subsidies to Capitalism", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - #2628b - Reviewed by Bagakis, Gus. "Toxic Loopholes: Failures and Future Prospects for Environmental Law", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - #2641b - Reviewed by Bruff, Ian. "Unravelling Gramsci: Hegemony and Passive Revolution in the Global Political Economy", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - #2632b - REviewed by Dymski, Gary. "The Credit Crunch", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - #2633b - Reviewed by Cheng, Zhiming. "China's External and Internal Challenges", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - #2634b - Reviewed by Basole, Amit. "Economics for Everyone: A Short Guide to the Economics of Capitalism", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - #2637b - Reviewed by Huato, Julio. "Keynes Solution: The Path to Global Economic Prosperity", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - #2638b - Reviewed by Ramirez, Miguel. "Latin American Neostructuralism", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - #2639 - Auerback, Nancy. "Delicious Peace Coffee" Marketing Community in Uganda", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - #2643b - Reviewed by Wicks-Lim, Jeannette. "The Living Wage: Lessons From the History of Economic Thought", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - #2644b - Reviewed by Belyaev, Demyan. "Prosperity Without Growth", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - #2645b - Reviewed by Bahce, Serdal. "Imperialism and Global Political Economy", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - #2648b - Reviewed by Shear, Boone. "Green Collar Economy", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - #2657b - Reviewed by Versieren, Jelle. "The Gramscian Moment", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - #2659b - Reviewed by Kostick, Conor. "Deep History", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - #2661b - Reviewed by Pietrykowski, Bruce. "Working in the Shadows", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - #2664 - Cipolla, Francisco. "Bonus Wages: Beyond Piece Wages", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - #2665b - Reviewed by Starr, Martha. "Theories of Social Capital: Researchers Behaving Badly", 2010 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - #2670b - Reviewed by Gunn, Christopher. "From Political Economy to Economics", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - #2672b - Reviewed by DiQuattro, Art. "Libertarian Communism", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - #2673b - Reviewed by Pimpare, Stephen. "Insufficient Funds", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - #2675 - Cumbers, Andrew. "Revisiting Public Ownership", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - #2677b - Reviewed by Major, Aaron. "Ideas and Ideology", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - #2678b - Reviewed by Weinberg, Bradley. "The Labour Movement in the Global South", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - #2680b - Reviewed by Saros, Daniel. "Free Trade Doesn't Work", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - #2682b - Reviewed by Dickens, Edwin. "Heterodox Macroeconomics", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - #2688b - Reviewed by Barnes, Thomas. "Theory as History", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - #2690b - Reviewed by Prasch, Robert. "The Value of Money", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - #2691b - Reviewed by Obeng-Odoom, Franklin. "Development and Globalization, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - #2696b - Reviewed by Wilson, Tamar Diana. "La Via Campesina: Globalization and the Power of Peasants", 2011 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - #2729 - Naidu, Sirisha. "Environmental Justice in Ohio", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - #2754b - Reviewed by Skinner, Curtis. "Unveiling Inequality", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - #2755b - Reviewed by Obeng-Odoom, Franklin. "Chocolate Nations", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - #2759b - Reviewed by Bateman, Milford. "Due Diligence", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - #2766b - Reviewed by Dugger, William. "Darwin's Conjecture", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - #2768b - Reviewed by Fisher, Jean. "Chivalry Carries the Day", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - #2687 - Bruno, Jossa. "Alienation and the Self-Managed Firm System", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - #2579 - Maniatis, Thanasis. "Does the State Benefit Labor?", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - # 2715 - Durand, Cedric. "Over-accumulation, Rising Costs and Unproductive Labour", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - # 2770 - Schmidt, Jeremy. "Property and the Right to Water: Toward a Non-liberal Commons, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - #2652 - Lapatsioras, Spyros. "Financialization and Marx", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - # 2748b - Reviewed by Andrews, Sean. "Raj Patel Essay", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - # 2785b - Reviewed by Herman, Barry. "Economic Policy and Human Rights", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - #2799b - Reviewed by Nelson, Anitra. "Human Economy: A Citizen's Guide", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - #2741 - Hahnel, Robin. "The Invisible Foot: A Tribute to E.K. Hunt", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - #2821b - Reviewed by Gunn, Christopher. "The Restructuring of Capitalism in Our Time", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - #2758b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "Class, Power and the State in Capitalist Society", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - #2778b - Reviewed by Cogliano, Jonathan. "Capital, Exploitation and Economic Crisis", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - #2775b - Reviewed by Komath, Chandran. "Globalization, Violence and World Governance", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - #2803b - Reviewed by Surprise, Kevin. "Global Crises and the Crisis of Global Leadership", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - #2804b - Reviewed by McCann, Laura. "The Cooperation Challenge of Economics and the Protection of Water Supplies", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - #2663 - Lippit, Victor. "Neoliberal Era and the Financial Crisis in the Light of SSA Theory", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - #2724 - Basu, Deepankar. "Comparative Growth Dynamics in a Discrete-time Circuit of Capital", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - #2780 - Sinha, Ajit. "Marx Law of the Falling Rate of Profit", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - #2771 - Orhangazi, Ozgur. "Contours of Alternative Policy Making in Venezuela", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - #2827b - Reviewed by Mongiovi, Gary. "Hahn and Economic Methodology", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - #2726b - Reviewed by Despain, Hans. "Ontology of Money", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - #2814b - Reviewed by Mader, Philip. "Confessions of a Microfinance Heretic", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - #2773 - Rieu, Dong-Min. "The Determination of the Monetary Expression of Labor Time", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - # 2781 - Tinel, Bruno. "Inter-firm Dependency and Employment Inequalities", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - # 2810b - Reviewed by Bahce, Serdal. "The Invisible Handcuffs of Capitalism", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - # 2822b - Reviewed by Hecht, Jason. "The Accidental Capitalist: A People's Story of the New China", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - #2840b - Reviewed by Vlcek, William. "Offshore:Tax Havens and the Rule of Global Crime", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - #2788 - Jossa, Bruno. "The Key Contradiction in Capitalist Systems", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - #2820 - Bayliss, Kate. "The Financialisation of Water", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - #2792 - Marois, Thomas. "Historical Precedents, Contemporary Manifestations", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - #2763 - Piovani, Chiara. "Class Power and China's Productivity Miracle", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - #2825 - Mohun, Simon. "Unproductive Labour in the US Economy", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - #2721 - Saros, Daniel. "Interlocking Turnover Continua and Structure of Capital", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - #2850 - Reati, Angelo. "A Note on Some Misunderstandings of Sraffa's System", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - #2869b - Reviewed by Chester, Lynne. "To Change or Reform Capitalism", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - #2864b - Reviewed by Bolzan, Alberto. "The Elgar Companion to Marxist Economics", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - #2591b - Reviewed by Krause, Laurence. "The Return of Depression Economics and the Crisis of 2008", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - #2858b - Reviewed by Nantha, Hemanath. "The Road From Mont Pelerin: Neoliberal Thought Collective", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - #2699b - Reviewed by Khanna, Sushil. "A New India? Critical Reflections", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - # 2717 - Baiman, Ron. "Unequal Exchange, Rentier Economy", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - #2865b - Reviewed by Fox, Kenneth. "Activists in City Hall", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - #2816b - Reviewed by Arora, Diksha. "Women, Gender and Development Reader", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - #2745b - Reviewed by GAssler, Robert. "Rethinking Macroeconomics for Sustainability", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - #2916b - Reviewed by Ranis, Peter. "Remaking Scarcity from Capitalist Inefficiency to Economic Democracy", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - #2889b - Reviewed by Gemici, Kurtulus. "Karl Polanyi: Limits of the Market", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - #2880b - Reviewed by Van Der Veen, Marjolein. In and Out of Crisis: Global Financial Meltdown", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - #2857b - Reviewed by Tansel, Cemal. "Challenge of Eurocentrism", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - #2877b - Reviewed by Bateman, Milford. "Zimbabwe Takes Back It's Land", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - #2862b - Reviewed by Funke, Jayson. "Political Economy of Nongovernmental Organizations", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - #2844b - Reviewed by Llorente, Renzo. "Voices From the Other Side", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - #2854 - Springer, Simon. "Postneoliberalism?", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - #2708 - Peacock, Mark. "Economic Policy Without Politics", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - #2396 - Olsen, Eric. "Unproductive Activity and Endogenous Technological Change", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - #2868 - Quero, Fernando. "Is Neoclassical Economics Scientific Knowledge Detached From Ethics?", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - #2812 - Feliz, Mariano. "Barriers and the Limits of Neodevelopmentalism", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - #2817 - Cuyvers, Ludo. "Was Henri De Man an Early Post-Keynesian Neo-Marxist?", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - #2843 - Zarembka, Paul. "Materialized Composition of Capital and It's Stability in the U.S.", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - #2907b - Reviewed by DeKadt, Maarten. "Reckless Endangerment", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - #2902b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "Private Equity Finance", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - #2900b - Reviewed by Willoughby, John. "Making of Global Capitalism", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - #2815b - Reviewed by Atbasi, Ferda. "Rosa Luxemburg and the Critique of Political Economy", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - #2835b - Reviewed by Erol, Mehmet. " Transition to Neoliberalism:, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - #2807 - Gradin, Sofa. "Radical Routes and Alternative Avenues", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - #2819 - Meyer, Leandro. "Fear or Greed? Duty or Solidarity?", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - #2751 - Lene, Alexandre and Bailly, Franck. "What Makes a Good Worker?", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - #2836 - Tymoigne, Eric. - "The Cost of Job Guarantee in the U.S.", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - #2779 - Miljikovic,Dragan. "Impact of External Pressure on Voting Outcomes in Transition Economics", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - # 2841 - Fernandez, Victor. "Global Value Chains in Global Political Networks", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - #2872 - Meng, Jie. "Two Kinds of MELT and Their Determinations", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - #2949b - Reviewed by "Down the Up Escalator", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 70)
    - #2913b - Reviewed by Peacock, Mark. "What Money Can't Buy", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - #2942b - Reviewed by Perelman, Michael. " Albert Hirschman", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - #2926b - Reviewed by Houseworth, Christina. "The State of Working America", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - #2796b - Reviewed by Cochrane, D. T. - "Diamonds and War: State, Capital and Labour in British Ruled Palestine", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - #2846 - Christensen, Kimberly. "He-session, She-session: The Gendered Impact of the Great Recession in the U.S.", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - #2892 - Bakir, Erdogan. "Capital Accumulation, Profitability and Crisis", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - #2735 - Das, Debarshi. "Changing Distribution of Land and Assets in Indian Agriculture", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - #2794 - Economakis, George. "Structural Analysis of the Greek Economy", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 78)